Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 2)
  - South Carolina
    - Clearwater
      - PP Aiken County, Reports, Clinics, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 60)
    - Columbia
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1961
        - 1961-1974 (Box 176, Folder 61)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 176)
      - Affiliation, PP Lex & Richland Counties, Correspondence from 1962
        - 1962-1974 (Box 176, Folder 62)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 176)
      - PP of Central South Carolina from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 176, Folder 63)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 176)
      - PP Richland & Lex Counties, 1964-1970 (Box 176, Folder 64-67)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1964 (Box 176, Folder 68)
      - PP Central South Carolina, Reports, Clinics from 1973
        - 1973 (Box 176, Folder 69)
        - 1980 (Box 176)
      - PP Richland & Lex Counties, Reports, General, 1964-1971 (Box 176, Folder 70)
      - PP Richland & Lex Counties, Reports, Members, 1964-1973 (Box 176, Folder 71)
      - PP Richland & Lex Counties, Publicity, 1963-1968 (Box 176, Folder 72)
    - Frogmore
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence, 1963-1971 (Box 176, Folder 73)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1964-1969 (Box 176, Folder 74)
      - PP Association Beaufort County, 1967-1971 (Box 176, Folder 75)
      - PP Association Beaufort County, 1964-1966 (Box 176, Folder 76)
      - Field Trips, 1962 (Box 176, Folder 77)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1966-1969 (Box 176, Folder 78)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members, 1964-1971 (Box 176, Folder 79)
      - Publicity, 1964-1969 (Box 176, Folder 80)
    - Southeast Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1964-1970 (Box 176, Folder 81)
  - South Dakota
    - Anti-Poverty, 1968-1971 (Box 176, Folder 82)
    - Contacts from 1966
      - 1965-1974 (Box 176, Folder 83)
      - 1976 (Box 176)
    - Hospitals, General, 1968-1971 (Box 176, Folder 84)
    - United Indian Association, 1977 (Box 176, Folder 85)
    - Projects & Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 176, Folder 86)
    - Public Health, 1965-1974 (Box 176, Folder 87)
    - Public Welfare, 1966-1971 (Box 176, Folder 88)
    - Schools, General, 1970-1972 (Box 176, Folder 89)
    - Sioux Falls, Planned Parenthood, 1966-1967 (Box 176, Folder 90)
    - Midwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1966-1971 (Box 176, Folder 91)
  - Tennessee
    - Southeast Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1964-1966 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1969 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Contacts from 1963
      - 1963-1974 (Box 177, Folder 3)
      - 1977 (Box 177)
    - Public Health, Family Planning Conference, 6/16-17/66, 1965-1966 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals, General, 1965-1970 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Legal from 1958
      - 1939-1971 (Box 177, Folder 6)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 177)
    - Medical Societies, 1966 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Projects, 1970 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Public Health, 1966-1972 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Public Health, 1963-1966 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Public Welfare from 1964
      - 1964-1970 (Box 177, Folder 11)
      - 1977 (Box 177)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1967-1970 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Schools, General from 1953
      - 1953-1969 (Box 177, Folder 13)
      - 1977 (Box 177)
    - Tennessee Association of Planned Parenthood, Affiliates from 1973
      - 1973 (Box 177, Folder 14)
      - 1975-1980 (Box 177)
    - Chattanooga
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1950-1966 (Box 177, Folder 15)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 177, Folder 16)
      - PP Association, 1963-1968 (Box 177, Folder 17)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1960 (Box 177, Folder 18)
    - Knoxville
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1964
        - 1964-1972 (Box 177, Folder 19)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 177)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 177, Folder 20)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 177)
      - PP Association of Knox County, Inc., Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 177, Folder 21)
      - PP from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 177, Folder 22)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 177)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1967-1969 (Box 177, Folder 23)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1965-1972 (Box 177, Folder 24)
      - PP of Knox County, Report, Field Trips, James S. Kohler, 1975 (Box 177, Folder 25)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1963 (Box 177, Folder 26)
    - Memphis
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 177, Folder 27)
        - 1977, 1980 (Box 177)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 177, Folder 28)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 177)
      - PP Association from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 177, Folder 29)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 177)
      - PP Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 177, Folder 30)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1966-1968 (Box 177, Folder 31)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1966-1972 (Box 177, Folder 32)
      - Publicity, 1970-1971 (Box 177, Folder 33)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1961 (Box 177, Folder 34)
    - Nashville
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 177, Folder 35)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 177)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 177, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 177)
      - PP Association of Nashville, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 177, Folder 37)
      - PP Association, Legal: Nashville Nurse Training Agreement, Vanderbilt University, 1977-1978 (Box 177, Folder 38)
      - PP Association
        - 1969-1974 (Box 177, Folder 39)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 177)
      - PP Committee, 1963-1968 (Box 177, Folder 40)
      - Nashville Family Planning Workshop for Tennessee Affiliates, 2/1-2/72, 1971-1972 (Box 177, Folder 41)
      - Training Center, Family Planning, 1968 (Box 177, Folder 42)
      - Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 11/63, 1962-1963 (Box 177, Folder 43)
      - Reports, General, 1966-1969 (Box 177, Folder 44)
      - Reports, Members, 1965-1973 (Box 177, Folder 45)
      - Publicity, 1963-1972 (Box 177, Folder 46)
      - Middle Tennessee Conference on Family Planning, 6/16-17/66, 1966 (Box 177, Folder 47)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1961 (Box 177, Folder 48)
    - Oak Ridge
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1962
        - 1961-1974 (Box 177, Folder 49)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 177)
      - Affiliation, PP Southern Mountains, Correspondence, from 1962
        - 1962-1974 (Box 177, Folder 50)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 177)
      - PP Association Southern Mountains, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 177, Folder 51)
      - PP of the Southern Mountains, 1975-1979 (Box 177, Folder 52)
      - PP Southern Mountains, 1967-1974 (Box 177, Folder 53)
      - PP Southern Mountains, 1964-1966 (Box 177, Folder 54)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1963 (Box 177, Folder 55)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1963-1968 (Box 177, Folder 56)
      - Reports, General, 1963-1970 (Box 177, Folder 57)
      - Reports, Members, 1964-1973 (Box 177, Folder 58)
      - Publicity, 1963-1972 (Box 177, Folder 59)
  - Texas
    - Anti-Poverty Program, 1965-1973 (Box 177, Folder 60)
    - Capitol Area Comprehensive Health Planning, Family Planning, 1972 (Box 177, Folder 61)
    - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 177, Folder 62)
    - Central Texas Family Planning Providers Meeting, 11/21/1972 (Box 177, Folder 63)
    - Central Texas Family Providers, 1972-1973 (Box 177, Folder 64)
    - Contacts from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 177, Folder 65)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 177)
    - Contacts, 1968-1970 (Box 177, Folder 66)
    - Contacts, 1962-1967 (Box 177, Folder 67)
    - Department of Community Affairs from 1973
      - 1973 (Box 177, Folder 68)
      - 1979 (Box 177)
    - Department of Health, Family Planning Meeting, Alice, Texas, Cap, PP, Region, 12/14-15/1971 (Box 177, Folder 69)
    - Department of HEW, Family Planning Services, Regional Program Director
      - 1970-1974 (Box 177, Folder 70)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 177)
    - Hospitals, Big Spring State Hospital, Grant Application, 1969 (Box 177, Folder 71)
    - Hospitals, General Correspondence, 1966-1974 (Box 177, Folder 72)
    - Legal from 1964
      - 1964-1974 (Box 178, Folder 1)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 178)
    - Life Planning/Health Services, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Life Planning/Health Services, Inc., 1979 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Lower Rio Grande Development Council, Health Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Meeting of All Family Planning Providers in Texas Health Region X, Harlington, Texas, 2/29/72-3/1/1972 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Migrant, 1969-1974 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Migrant, 1962-1968 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Migrant, Field Trips, 1961-1962 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Multiple County Family Planning, 1971-1973 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Projects, 1969-1973 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Public Health from 1964
      - 1964-1972 (Box 178, Folder 11)
      - 1979 (Box 178)
    - Public Welfare from 1967
      - 1967-1974 (Box 178, Folder 12)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 178)
    - Public Welfare, 1964-1966 (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - South Texas Family Planning Corporation from 1972
      - 1972-1974 (Box 178, Folder 14)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 178)
    - Texas Coalition for Family Planning, 1976 (Box 178, Folder 15)
    - Texas Board of Medical Examiners, 1976-1980 (Box 178, Folder 16)
    - Texas Confederation of Planned Parenthood Affiliates from 1973
      - 1973-1974 (Box 178, Folder 17)
      - 1975, 1979 (Box 178)
    - Texas Department of Human Resources, 1978 (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - Texas Environmental Coalition, 1971-1972 (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Texas Family Institute, 1977 (Box 178, Folder 20)
    - Texas Family Planning Association, 1976-1978 (Box 178, Folder 21)
    - Texas Health Code, 1974 (Box 178, Folder 22)
    - Texas Medical Association, 1971-1973 (Box 178, Folder 23)
    - Texas PP Medical Foundation, 1973 (Box 178, Folder 24)
    - Texas Medical Practice Act, 1976-1977 (Box 178, Folder 25)
    - PERC (Public Education & Research Committee) from 1975
      - 1974 (Box 178, Folder 26)
      - 1975 (Box 178)
    - Statistics: Birth Rates & Venereal Diseases Rates, 1975 (Box 178, Folder 27)
    - Texas United Community Legislative Forum, 1973 (Box 178, Folder 28)
    - State Board of Pharmacy from 1965
      - 1965-1973 (Box 178, Folder 29)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 178)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1966-1970 (Box 178, Folder 30)
    - Texas United Community Services, 1972 (Box 178, Folder 31)
    - Weddington, Sarah (House of Representatives) from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 178, Folder 32)
      - 1976 (Box 178)
    - Schools, General from 1959
      - 1959-1973 (Box 178, Folder 33)
      - 1975, 1979 (Box 178)
    - Agricultural & Mechanical College, 1955-1969 (Box 178, Folder 34)
    - Baylor University, 1957-1972 (Box 178, Folder 35)
    - North Texas State College, 1953-1962 (Box 178, Folder 36)
    - University of Texas Cope, 1969-1970 (Box 178, Folder 37)
    - University of Texas, 1955-1974 (Box 178, Folder 38)
    - Texas Association of PP Affiliates, 1975-1979 (Box 178, Folder 39)
    - Abilene, PP Association of West Central Texas, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 178, Folder 40)
    - Alice
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 178, Folder 41)
        - 1975 (Box 178)
      - Affiliation, PP Jim Wells County, Correspondence from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 178, Folder 42)
        - 1975 (Box 178)
      - PP Jim Wells County from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 178, Folder 43)
        - 1975 (Box 178)
    - Amarillo
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1973 (Box 178, Folder 44)
        - 1977, 1979 (Box 178)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 178, Folder 45)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 178)
      - Panhandle PP Association from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 178, Folder 46)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 178)
      - PP Committee of the Panhandle from 1965
        - 1965-1971 (Box 178, Folder 47)
        - 1977 (Box 178)
      - Reports, General, 1969 (Box 178, Folder 48)
      - Reports, Members from 1968
        - 1968-1973 (Box 178, Folder 49)
        - 1976 (Box 178)
    - Athens, Henderson County PP Clinic, 1970-1973 (Box 178, Folder 50)
    - Austin
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1949
        - 1949-1974 (Box 178, Folder 51)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 178)
      - PP Center from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 178, Folder 52)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 178)
      - PP Center, 1964-1965 (Box 178, Folder 53)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1963 (Box 178, Folder 54)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1965-1968 (Box 178, Folder 55)
      - Reports, General, 1966-1968 (Box 178, Folder 56)
      - Reports, Members from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 178, Folder 57)
        - 1975 (Box 178)
      - Publicity, 1964-1973 (Box 178, Folder 58)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1948
        - 1948-1973 (Box 178, Folder 59)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 178)
    - Beaumont
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1962-1966 (Box 178, Folder 60)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence, 1961-1966 (Box 178, Folder 61)
      - PP, 1964-1965 (Box 178, Folder 62)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1964 (Box 178, Folder 63)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members, 1963-1966 (Box 178, Folder 64)
      - PP Association, Publicity, 1960-1966 (Box 178, Folder 65)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1963 (Box 178, Folder 66)
    - Brownsville
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1972 (Box 178, Folder 67)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 178)
      - Affiliation, PP Cameron County, Correspondence from 1967
        - 1966-1974 (Box 178, Folder 68)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 178)
      - PP of Cameron County, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 178, Folder 69)
      - PP of Cameron County from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 178, Folder 70)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 178)
      - PP of Greater Brownsville, 1964-1972 (Box 178, Folder 71)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1966-1972 (Box 178, Folder 72)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members, 1966-1972 (Box 178, Folder 73)
    - Bryan, PP of Brazos County, 1966-1967 (Box 178, Folder 74)
    - Corpus Christi
      - Affiliation, Budgets, Audits, Bylaws from 1960
        - 1960-1974 (Box 178, Folder 75)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 178)
      - Affiliation, South Texas PP Center, Correspondence from 1960
        - 1960-1974 (Box 178, Folder 76)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 178)
      - South Texas PP Center, Merger, 1971 (Box 178, Folder 77)
      - PP South Texas from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 178, Folder 78)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 178)
      - PP South Texas, 1963-1965 (Box 178, Folder 79)
      - Field Trips, 1959-1963 (Box 178, Folder 80)
      - South Texas PP Center, Reports, General, 1967-1971 (Box 179, Folder 1)
      - South Texas PP Center, Reports, Members, 1965-1971 (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Anti-Poverty Program, Press Seminar, 7/1965 (Box 179, Folder 3)
      - South Texas PP Center, Publicity, 1963-1967 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Crystal City
      - Affiliation, PP Center, Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 179, Folder 5)
      - PP Center, 1965-1970 (Box 179, Folder 6)
      - Reports, Members, 1965 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Dallas
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 179, Folder 8)
        - 1977 (Box 179)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 179, Folder 9)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 179)
      - PP Association of Northeast Texas, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 179, Folder 10)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 179, Folder 11)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 179, Folder 12)
      - PP of Northeast Texas, 1975-1979 (Box 179, Folder 13)
      - Site Assessment & Market Research (Self-Sustaining Clinics), 1980 (Box 179, Folder 14)
      - PP, 1962-1974 (Box 179, Folder 15-19)
      - Field Trips, 1959-1964 (Box 179, Folder 20)
      - Reports, General from 1962
        - 1962-1969 (Box 179, Folder 21)
        - 1975 (Box 179)
      - Reports, Members, 1963-1967 (Box 179, Folder 22)
      - Publicity
        - 1963-1969 (Box 179, Folder 23)
        - 1977 (Box 179)
      - Workshop, 11/12/62, 1962-1963 (Box 179, Folder 24)
      - Conference on "Population Crisis," 5/17-19/1960 (Box 179, Folder 25)
      - Family Planning in Dallas, Joy G. Dryfoos, 7/1968 (Box 179, Folder 26)
    - Del Rio
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1970-1973 (Box 179, Folder 27)
      - Affiliation, PP Association Val Verde County, Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 179, Folder 28)
      - PP of Val Verde County, 1969-1973 (Box 179, Folder 29)
    - Eagle Pass
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1968-1970 (Box 179, Folder 30)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 179, Folder 31)
      - PP Maverick County, 1967-1972 (Box 179, Folder 32)
      - Reports, Members, 1968-1970 (Box 179, Folder 33)
    - El Paso
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1949-1973 (Box 179, Folder 34)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 179)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1973 (Box 179, Folder 35)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 179)
      - PP Center of El Paso from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 179, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 179)
      - PP Center, 1966-1972 (Box 179, Folder 37)
      - PP Center, 1964-1965 (Box 179, Folder 38)
      - Field Trips, 1959-1963 (Box 179, Folder 39)
      - Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 11/62, 1962 (Box 179, Folder 40)
      - PP Center, Reports, General, 1965-1966 (Box 179, Folder 41)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 179, Folder 42)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 179)
      - PP Center, Publicity, 1960-1968 (Box 179, Folder 43)
    - Fort Worth
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1949
        - 1949-1972 (Box 179, Folder 44)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 179)
      - Affiliation, PP Center, Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974, 1980 (Box 179, Folder 45)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 179)
      - PP Center of Fort Worth from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 179, Folder 46)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 179)
      - PP Center, 1964-1971 (Box 179, Folder 47)
      - Teenage Sexuality Seminar, 9/18-19/1975 (Box 179, Folder 48)
      - Reports, Members, 1963-1971 (Box 179, Folder 49)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1948-1964 (Box 179, Folder 50)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1963 (Box 179, Folder 51)
    - Harlingen, PP Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 179, Folder 52)
    - Houston
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1950
        - 1950-1973 (Box 179, Folder 53)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 179)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1950
        - 1960-1974 (Box 179, Folder 54)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 179)
      - PP Association of Houston, Reports, Clinics from 1973
        - 1973 (Box 179, Folder 55)
        - 1980 (Box 179)
      - PP of Houston, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 179, Folder 56)
      - PP of Houston, 1975-1979 (Box 179, Folder 57)
      - PP of Houston, 1972-1974 (Box 179, Folder 58)
      - PP Center, 1967-1971 (Box 179, Folder 59)
      - PP Center, 1963-1966 (Box 179, Folder 60)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1963 (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Publicity, 1976 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - PP Center, Reports, General from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 180, Folder 3)
        - 1978 (Box 180)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members from 1965
        - 1965-1970 (Box 180, Folder 4)
        - 1975 (Box 180)
    - Kingsville
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1971 (Box 180, Folder 5)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 180)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence
        - 1968-1974 (Box 180, Folder 6)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 180)
      - PP Chaparral County, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 180, Folder 7)
      - PP Association of Chaparral County from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 180, Folder 8)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 180)
      - PP, 1966-1972 (Box 180, Folder 9)
      - Reports, Members, 1969-1972 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Laredo
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1971 (Box 180, Folder 11)
        - 1975 (Box 180)
      - PP Correspondence from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 180, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 180)
      - PP of Webb County, Inc., Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 180, Folder 13)
      - PP Association of Webb County from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 180, Folder 14)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 180)
      - PP Committee, 1962 (Box 180, Folder 15)
      - PP, Reports, Members from 1969
        - 1969-1973 (Box 180, Folder 16)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 180)
      - Field Trips, 1962 (Box 180, Folder 17)
    - Lockhart
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1967-1970 (Box 180, Folder 18)
      - Affiliation, PP Caldwell County, Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box 180, Folder 19)
      - PP Caldwell County, 1965-1973 (Box 180, Folder 20)
      - Reports, Members, 1968-1971 (Box 180, Folder 21)
    - Lubbock
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1963
        - 1963-1972 (Box 180, Folder 22)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 180)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1963
        - 1963-1974 (Box 180, Folder 23)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 180)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1965 (Box 180, Folder 24)
      - PP of Lubbock from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 180, Folder 25)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 180)
      - PP Association, 1964-1971 (Box 180, Folder 26)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1953-1967 (Box 180, Folder 27)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1964-1973 (Box 180, Folder 28)
      - PP, Publicity, 1960-1967 (Box 180, Folder 29)
      - County Family Project, 1970 (Box 180, Folder 30)
    - McAllen (Formerly in Mission)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1978-1980 (Box 180, Folder 31)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 180, Folder 32)
        - 1977 (Box 180)
      - Affiliation, PP Hidalgo County, Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 180, Folder 33)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1964
        - 1964-1974 (Box 180, Folder 34)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 180)
      - PP Hidalgo County from 1978 (empty) (Box 180, Folder 35)
      - PP Association Hidalgo County
        - 1967-1974 (Box 180, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 180)
      - PP Association Hidalgo County, 1964-1974 (Box 180, Folder 37)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1965-1967 (Box 180, Folder 38)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1964-1969 (Box 180, Folder 39)
    - Midland
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1966-1968 (Box 180, Folder 40)
      - PP Correspondence, Affiliation from 1965
        - 1965-1971 (Box 180, Folder 41)
        - 1975 (Box 180)
      - Permian Basin PP, 1964-1972 (Box 180, Folder 42)
      - Reports, General, 1955-1968 (Box 180, Folder 43)
      - Reports, Members, 1966-1970 (Box 180, Folder 44)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1962 (Box 180, Folder 45)
    - New Braunfels
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1966-1969 (Box 180, Folder 46)
      - Affiliation, PP Comal County Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 180, Folder 47)
      - PP Comal County, 1965-1966 (Box 180, Folder 48)
    - Odessa
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1968
        - 1968-1970 (Box 180, Folder 49)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 180)
      - Merger: Odessa, Midland from 1970
        - 1970-1971 (Box 180, Folder 50)
        - 1978 (Box 180)
      - Affiliation, Permian Basin PP, Inc. (formerly Ector County), 1980 (Box 180, Folder 51)
      - Affiliation, Permian Basin PP, Inc. (Formerly Ector County) from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 180, Folder 52)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 180)
      - Permian Basin PP from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 180, Folder 53)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 180)